southernsavers.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy Policy :: Southern Savers

This document was last updated on November 27, 2009.

**1\. Acknowledgment and acceptance of terms**

Southern Savers LLC is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing www.southernsavers.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Southern Savers LLC’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

**2\. Participating Merchant Policies**

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in Southern Savers LLC services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

**3. Information We Collect and How We Use It** Southern Savers LLC collects certain information from and about its users two ways: directly from our Web Server logs, and the user.

 **a. ****Web Server Logs**.

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Web page you linked to our site from.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

  1. **Personal Information Users**

Visitors to our website can register for certain services or giveaways. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number other relevant information.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission.

**4. Use of Web Beacons or GIF files**

Southern Savers Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow Southern Savers LLC to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Southern Savers LLC may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Southern Savers LLC prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

**5. Changes to this Statement**

Southern Savers LLC has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**6\. Contacting Us**

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at jenny @ southernsavers . com, or send your comments to :

Southern Savers LLC **Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel** 7001 St Andrews Rd #311 Columbia, SC 29212 

Southern Savers LLC will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
